Emergency. ETA?
AAAR!
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Aaaaahhhhhhhhh!
Aaaahhhhhhhhhhh!
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, ah, ah.
Ultima Ratio Hecate II.
Hecate I
don't
know.
How do I know?
I'll be trying to make you feel.
I'm trying to make you feel.
I'm trying to keep you.
A painless pain.
I'll be trying to keep you.
I'll be able to come and see.
I'll be able to keep you.
I'm trying to keep you.
I'm not even happy.
That is a moment of silence?.
Let it be red.
I'll see you in the end of the day.
Let it be red,
The sound of the beginning will change the
Yo, Dine.
You sure you got the right info?
They're coming or what?
They're coming, all right.
I checked the route myself. So relax.
I bet they're busy clearing
some big-ass monster spawn.
That means your cut will be bigger
this time, so no complaining.
Dude, no one's complaining.
Since we're talking about it, ain't
these the same jokers we hit last week?
They could have wised up to
us and changed their route.
All that squad does is hunt monsters.
They don't care how many
times they get attacked,
because they'll just make up
for it on their next hunt.
For player-hunter squads like
us, they make the perfect target.
They move by algorithm,
just like the monsters.
As far as I'm concerned, they're chumps.
Damn straight.
As for weapons, they're geared up with
optical guns for hunting monsters.
But we've got defense shields, so as
long as those are up, it's easy pickings.
Well, what if they got smart?
Like, what if they're
ready for us this time?
We hit them not too long ago, right?
I doubt they got their hands on
enough live ammo guns that fast.
By now, they might have one firearm
for support, but that's about it.
And besides, we got the best
sniper in GGO watching our backs.
We've got all our bases covered.
Right, Xenon?
Yep.
Guess I can't argue with that.
With a crack shot like Xenon up
here, things are looking good.
It's better than good.
Well, if.
It's a big if, but still.
If she missed, I'd be cool with that.
It'll take them about a minute to
figure out where the shot came from.
While they're doing that,
I'll be in position.
I'll hose them down and rake in the money.
Easy, cowboy.
Hey, doll face.
I was wondering, what
you doing after this?
I found a gun shop with
an awesome inventory.
Maybe we could go get something
to eat or maybe do something else.
You know what I mean.
I don't know what you mean, January.
Besides, there's stuff I
have to do when I log out.
Oh, come on, doll face. What's the stuff?
Wait, are you still in school?
Oh, that's kind of hot.
You got a report, too.
Yeah, right.
Lay off her, January.
Don't put her on the spot like that.
We're working, so don't bring
up the real world in here.
Yeah, man.
This ain't the time or place
to respect your solo status.
Like, you guys can talk.
When's the last time
either of you got lucky?
Last night with your sister.
Knock it off. Stay sharp. Got him.
About time they showed up to the party.
Yep, it's them.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
That's one more than last week.
We got four optical blasters in the front.
I see one large-caliber laser rifle,
not a problem, and a guy with
a mini-me, he goes down first.
The new guy in the back, he's got a
cloak on, can't see what he's carrying.
He's wearing a cloak? Yeah.
Maybe it's him, that death gun
guy everyone's talking about.
Huh, no way.
What, you believe in fairy tales now?
He looks like he's strength-filled.
Probably just a courier, though.
If anything, I bet he's carrying the
squad's ammo, energy packs, and drops.
Eh, we can ignore him.
I'm getting a bad vibe
from the guy in back.
I think we should take him out
before anyone else. No way.
He's not carrying any weapons.
Maybe he is, maybe he isn't.
He's an unknown, so he's a risk.
I hear what you're saying,
but there's also a mini-me out
there, and that's a problem.
If he starts lighting us up and those
blasters move in, it's gonna get ugly.
Understood.
I'll drop the guy with the mini-me first.
But my second bullet's got Mr.
Cloak's name on it.
Hate to interrupt you guys,
but they're closing on us.
They're at 2,500 meters.
All right.
We're gonna stick with
the original plan and
wait for him in the
shadow of that building.
Sinon, call out if the situation changes.
Wait for my order to fire.
Roger.
All right, move out.
I'm in position. Roger.
Targets haven't changed
their course or their speed.
They're 400 meters from you,
1,500 from me. Pretty far.
Can you make the shot? No sweat.
Okay, then. Fire when ready.
I'm counting on you, Xenon.
Roger.
This pressure this anxiety this fear
1500 meters that's nothing like tossing a
lot of paper into a trash can no way this
is nothing like how it felt that day?
Next.
Can't change position.
I cleared the first target, but
I couldn't pop the second one.
Roger that.
Sit tight up there, you hear?
Go, go, go!
He's got a minigun!
They're not late because
their hunt was running long.
They're moving slow in the field.
Because the weight of that
minigun's got a movement penalty.
Let's go.
Score!
Ha!
I knew it.
This op's gonna be a cakewalk.
What was that?
If he can smile in the middle of a
firefight, he must be pretty brave.
We're crazy.
Either way, he's mine.
Duck!
Crap!
Don't let him get closer!
Fire!
Roger that!
Gotta find some cover, but where?
Where, damn it, where? Where?
S-Sinon?
Sinon, are you hit?
Bastards, they teamed up
with a freaking bodyguard.
Bodyguard?
It's that guy with the minigun.
He's a macho prick,
calls himself behemoth.
Well, we can't keep sitting here
cause they're gonna wipe us out.
That minigun's only got
so much ammo to fire.
If we attack him at once, he'll panic
and burn through the rest of it.
Jin and Miss, you take the left flank.
Dyne and I'll come in from the right.
Arashi, you stay here and cover us.
That's crazy.
What about the three guys out
there carrying the blasters?
Even if we rush them, our
defense shields aren't enough.
Right, but their blasters can't
fire as fast as a live ammo gun.
We can just dodge them.
Screw that!
If we go charging out there, that
minigun will turn us into confetti!
Sorry, but we're packing it in.
It's better if we logged out right now.
At least we'll be able to get away.
Hey.
You don't get away from
things by logging out.
Are you nuts?
This is a game, for Christ's sakes.
Think about it.
Even if we charge them, we just die.
Then die! Huh?
It is a game,
so you can at least have the balls to
face death here instead of whining.
We can do this.
If you can distract a minigun for
three seconds, I can take him out.
Yeah. Good.
Then we'll split up and attack
him from both sides, got it?
Got it.
Go!
Die! Cover me!
How do you like that, punk?
Oh!
Screw you!
Yes!
Nice going.
Now, I've got to figure out how
to get into Behemoth's blind spot.
I better move fast, or he's going
to get a beat on my location.
Bullets are flying, and he's
got the guts to smile like that.
Maybe I will, too, when I kill him.
Oh, my God.
You're dead.
I don't know.
I love you.
Damn it.
I gotta get stronger.
I've got a new trick up my sleeve.
Please all help me!
I'm coming!
Lisbeth!
Oh, no!
Yay!
Let's see what we got.
Please tell me that's the last of it. Hmm.
I think I pretty much got
everything I need now.
You want to keep going some more?
You always hook us up at your shop, so
if you need more, we don't mind helping.
Thanks, guys.
Although, hmm, we sort of picked
this place clean, didn't we?
Let's take a break and let them respawn.
Okay.
They're so into each other.
It's not fair, damn it. How now?
Ugh, doesn't matter if
they're at school or here.
They can't keep their
hands off each other.
You mean they're like this at school, too?
All day, every day.
Why?
Asuna, there's something important
I've been wanting to tell you.
I've never moved in the past.
I've never been in a past.
I've never been in a
past. I couldn't be seen.
I've never been in my past.
I've never been in this pain.
All of us at once.
If it's empty?
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Next time, Memories of Blood.